militaryonesource.mil 2011-11-23

# Military OneSource

In partnership with the Army, Marine Corps, Navy, and Air Force, Military One Source helps Service Members and their families with a variety of issues that may improve the quality of their lives. Military OneSource Online may ask for your name, e-mail, and other information so that we can provide you with resources that are most relevant to you. Because privacy is something relevant to all of us, we take every measure to protect yours.

Whenever you submit personal information to Military OneSource Online, it travels through Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to attempt to protect your confidentiality. The information technology staff regularly checks for the success and failure of system processes and services to maintain Web security and integrity. While this is the most up-to-date technology to securely transfer information over the Internet, the confidentiality of your e-mail cannot be guaranteed.

Conversations and other communications with Military OneSource consultants remain private. Military OneSource Online does not share personally identifiable information with vendors or other agents, companies, or services without your expressed permission. Your personal information is used only to enhance your experience with Military OneSource Online; it is not sold, rented, loaned, or transferred to any unrelated third parties. Although aggregated statistics about site usage are prepared to better serve our customer base, no identifiable information is tracked in these statistical reports. However, Military OneSource is obligated to provide certain reportable information to the appropriate military authority for discussions concerning your safety or the safety of others. Military OneSource is also mandated to notify the proper state agencies in these instances.

Furthermore, DoD Directives allow for restricted reporting of sexual assault and domestic abuse. Restricted reporting means that an active duty victim of sexual assault or an active duty or family member victim of domestic abuse can contact identified individuals for assistance without triggering a military investigation or command notification. Sexual assault and domestic abuse are not reportable events if the victim chooses to make a restricted report to identified individuals; however, Military OneSource is obligated to provide certain reportable information to the appropriate military authority. This would include concerns about your safety, the safety of others, illegal practices, and child or special needs family member abuse/neglect. Military OneSource is also mandated to notify the proper state agencies in these instances.

No participant has the right to infringe upon another participant’s ability to obtain information on this site by methods such as, but not limited to, harassment, insults, or invasion of privacy. Messages posted or sent should not include any language or visual or audio component that could be construed as unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, fraudulent, harmful, abusive, hateful, pornographic, or in violation of any law, including the property rights of others or the privacy or publicity right of others.

Military OneSource Online offers links to external Web sites for educational purposes. No guarantee about any external Web site's security is made by Military OneSource Online. Additionally, Military OneSource Online cannot control the use of "cookies" or any other such tracking devices that are used by external Web sites to record personal information. The external Web sites are solely responsible for how they use any personal information that you provide to them. If you have questions about security provisions for any external Web site, review that site's disclaimer or privacy statement.

* * *
